<PropertyList include="777-set-common.xml">

    <sim n="0">
        <description>Boeing 777-200LR</description>
        <aero>777-200LR</aero>
        <max-payload type="double">440000</max-payload>
        <startup>
            <splash-texture>Aircraft/777/splash-200LR.png</splash-texture>
        </startup>

        <model n="0">
            <path>Aircraft/777/Models/777-200LR.xml</path>
            <livery>
                <file type="string">BA</file>
            </livery>
            <lights>
                <file type="string">BA</file>
            </lights>
        </model>
        <view n="0">
            <config n="0">
                <z-offset-m type="double">-22.84</z-offset-m>
            </config>
        </view>
        <view n="100">
            <config n="0">
                <z-offset-m type="double">-22.84</z-offset-m>
            </config>
        </view>
        <view n="101">
            <config n="0">
                <z-offset-m type="double">-22.84</z-offset-m>
            </config>
        </view>

        <help n="0">
            <title>777-200LR</title>
            <text>=====B777-200(LR) startup guide by SP-WKA=====

0. remember to:
a) set the correct QNH (pressure) when below transition level
b) set the fuel to a proper level in each tank (so you dont mess with the sliders when airborne :D)
c) you can use ctrl+c to reveal all usable buttons and knobs

1. prepare systems:
a) turn on the battery, taxi lights, rotating beacon and panel lights if you need it (button is placed)
to tle left, left from the BCN light button.
b) turn the APU knob clockwise (the knob next to the APU GEN), wait 1min for it to start-up
c) set APU knob to the middle position
d) open APU and L, C, R ISLN bleed air valves to supply L and R ENG starters with compressed air
e) turn on all 4 hydraulic pumps/valves. 2 in the center are for the flaps and spoilers (both
pumps MUST be enabled), the same with the other two, they are for landing gear. the
buttons are between electrical and fuel part of the panel.

2. prepare engines:
a) start fuel pumps. there are 6: 2 for each tank. to enable fuel flow from a tank, you have
to enable BOTH (just like with the hydraulics) pumps.
b) enable the engine starters (you can turn on both one after another, but thats not really realistic)
c) after N1 reach ~45, engine should be running on its own, self sustaining, fuel cutoff valves open
automatically. eicas shows up a message that L(R) ENG STARTER is on.
d) turn on both engine generators
e), turn off APU (knob position 1) and BAT

3. jettisonning fuel:
a) just press the JETTISON ARM button, its hidden behind some knob in the right part of the OH panel,
go to $0 a) if you cant find it
b) monitor the fuel levels, press the button again to stop the process. (jettisonning will automatically
stop when theres ~1000 gallons in each tank)
c) fuel flow is 30 gallons per second.

4. using the crossfeed (XFEED VALVE/PUMP):
a) enable FWD xfeed pump and AFTER IT enable AFT pump. if you mess this, it wont work and you will have
to repeat.
b) watch the fuel indicators on the eicas as the fuel level gets equalized in both tanks, left and right.
c) fuel flow is set to 4 gallons per second.
</text>
        </help>

        <menubar n="0">
            <default n="0">
                <menu n="100">
                    <label>777-200LR</label>
                </menu>
            </default>
        </menubar>

        <weight n="1">
            <!--  328 pax max @ 180 lbs -->
            <name>Pax/Baggage</name>
            <weight-lb type="double">44840</weight-lb>
            <max-lb type="double">131000</max-lb>
            <min-lb type="double">0</min-lb>
        </weight>
    </sim>

    <consumables n="0">
        <fuel n="0">
            <tank n="3"><name>Rear A</name></tank>
            <tank n="4"><name>Rear B</name></tank>
            <tank n="5"><name>Rear C</name></tank>
        </fuel>
    </consumables>

    <instrumentation n="0">
        <cdu n="0">
            <ident>
                <model>777-200LR</model>
                <engines>GE90-115B</engines>
            </ident>
        </cdu>
    </instrumentation>

    <autopilot n="0">
        <constant>
            <flare-base type="double">0.2</flare-base>
			<descent-profile-high-base type="double">0.23</descent-profile-high-base>
			<descent-profile-high-rate type="double">-0.00084337</descent-profile-high-rate>
			<descent-profile-low-base type="double">0.17</descent-profile-low-base>
			<descent-profile-low-rate type="double">-0.00033133</descent-profile-low-rate>
        </constant>
    </autopilot>

</PropertyList>
